3.2.1. do
goo
Wow!
It's so beautiful!
So beautiful!
You can eat it in a flash, in a blink of an eye.
I'm doing it with a tiny one.
Delicious.
It's warm.
At the end, we dance to Versio's music.
Some of you came yesterday, too!
Oh, my God! Great, great, great!
Prince is awesome! Seriously great!
Oh, it's really great, this!
Come on, Umedagata-san, let's go.
We'll be waiting for you.
I'm off!
Thank you for watching.
Through the glass is close, but at least to this group scene.
From here regardei what a place in this scenery ça
la
Thank you for watching.
I was actually connecting the shopping district with the relay.
There's a god named Gubu Singh in Gubu.
There's a feeling I created.
You're wearing it on your in-shirt.
I've been pulled for so many years
I made it with food.
You're even wearing it on your in-shirt.
I can't make something that's already made.
It's like a character.
You can take a picture with him.
That's a good idea.
About this size?
Big enough to fit in.
About the same size?
Barely.
Oh, my God.
Thank you very much for watching.
Good night.
I'll see what I can do today.
Let's see what we're going to see today.
I'm excited to see what we're going to see today.
I'm looking forward to AppliCare.
I'll do that... now... the elephant's up.
I think that's what they're for... to keep going up and down.
I saw your finger, too.
What did you go to today?
I went to a slide and a nap, right?
Good night.
Finished scumball distress
wash
litigation
sicz
Gentleen from me
And при tiế
This is Silkworm
I'm from
Forest School
tratar
family blur
without knowing the end of the road
why sometimes
the ninja's favorite cricure will come to this stage!
it will end beautifully
Oja trabalh
I'm sure it will be late in the hour
A step will be taken
We're ready.
That's a lot.
I tried to put in a lot
Very convenient.
Congratulations
Congratulations!
From now on, I want to say what I want to say, even if it's not in the middle of a sentence, I want to do it traditionally.
I would like to talk about these things while explaining them to the audience.
So I hope you will tell us what you want to say only this time, or something like that.
Yes, sir.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm off.
I'll see you later.
Opening.
Here's the opening.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for watching.
We'll be on in a few minutes.
Seven.
Six.
5 seconds ago
10 min.
Yes, please.
Please stage
I'll read and flush.
Good afternoon.
Much better.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning
Good morning. - Good morning.
I see you're here.
Thank you very much.
So here we are.
From the Munakata Festival
I'd like to send you a live broadcast from the Goo Goo Channel.
I'd like to send you a live broadcast from the Munakata Festival.
Thank you very much.
I'm from Kurume and I'm from Kurume.
I'm from Kurume.
My name is R. Fujimoto.
Pleased to meet you.
Let me introduce myself in turn.
I'm a DB comedian.
My name is Kirara of the Rainbow Troupe.
I'm from Orange Star High School.
I'm Kirara Nijigumi, a pitch-perfect college girl
I'm Kirara of the Rainbow Gumi, the person inside Beadle
I have a lot of information
And
We batention itself
Darn.
I'm Ai Kiyama
I'm Kiina Haruno
I am Sakura Seta
I am Riroa Aoi
I am Miyu Yanagi
Pleased to meet you.
Excellent.
Very spacious.
It's nice.
Good weather.
Weather's not too hot, just right.
It's great.
There's some shrines and stuff.
And we, the Goo Goo Channel...
Come and see us.
Our efforts so far have been
with a lot of people in Kyushu.
with many people in Kyushu.
We've even filmed on location.
I'm also from Kurume.
I did PR in the local shopping arcade.
Based on these efforts and relationships
and the relationships we've made so far
For the Munakata Festival
I have been preparing various projects for the Munakata Festival.
I'll be showing you what we've been up to.
We are going to deliver them to you through this live broadcast.
This time, people from outside of Munakata
participated in the festival.
the world, which was not there even now.
We would like to bring you an event that you can participate in.
I would like to bring you an event that you can participate in.
So, let's take a look at the schedule.
I'd like to take a look at the schedule.
Are you going to be on the live streaming?
Do you want to make a letter or something?
Oh, yeah!
Let's dance together!
Oh, dancing, yes!
That's what I'm talking about.
What's up?
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Come on, come on.
Oh!
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
hip
Hooray!
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
속い front and pinch Yano eyes were attached Plain
me Did you think right?
Thank you for watching!
Amazing! Oh, there is a Murakata festival, isn't there?
It's nice.
I like it.
I'm thinking.
Yes, I understand. Excuse me, please.
Yes, well, I guess it's time for you to go,
Ah!
I would like to ask all of you who are in the booth to sit down at the Murakata festival,
I would like you all to sit down at the Murakata festival.
We will be there later as well, so please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
We will see you later.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
Yes, I will.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Please take care of them.
Okay.
Fujimoto-san will be here later, right?
Thank you for your hard work.
I would like to go to the Murakata festival.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
Well, it was early in the morning, but so many people came,
I'm really looking forward to the future.
I'm off to the concert now!
Good luck!
I'll do my best!
It's already amazing, the sense of art!
Hello and best regards
Nice to meet you.
Please introduce yourself again.
I'm an art performer.
My name is Lisa Karalizm, and I'm an art performer.
This time, I'm going to do the cover of a picture book.
A cover?
Am I allowed to say that?
I am going to draw a picture related to the sea.
I've been working on environmental issues.
But it's not finished after I've drawn it.
I'm going to draw it after I'm done.
I'd like you and Mr. Fujimoto to participate in this project.
I'd like them to participate in the project.
plus the participation of our customers.
I'm going to complete the project with your participation.
We will make it together.
Thank you very much for watching!
I'm going to say it right now.
Oh, oh, what is it, a rainbow?
Wow, a rainbow!
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Oh, wow!
Congratulations!
Yes! You've seen the performance of Bunkan.
But, let's see, after this, we're going to make the ocean even more beautiful.
But in order to make people want to clean up the ocean even more...
I'd like to ask you to pollute the ocean.
Oh, pollute the ocean? Is that okay?
Can I just splash it?
Where are you going? What do you mean, "trash"?
I'm scared! Are you sure?
Oh, my God!
I'm telling you, it's just a plastic bottle of garbage.
This, you know, this, uh, this, uh, this is okay?
Wow! I wrote it in the best place!
It's okay, right? It's okay.
Yes, if the parents are willing to support us.
Your boots are so cool!
Really? Are you okay? Can't you afford it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, hold on a second.
I'll get you to write it down.
You're so cool.
Oh, my God, you're a beautiful girl.
What's your name?
Kii.
Kii?
She draws hearts, Kii.
They're getting very dirty.
Oh, there are three of them.
So, now that we're all done here, what's going to happen now?
Yes, I'd like to put this painting in the, uh, in the, uh, in the Trigirl booth.
Yes, right here on the right hand side.
Yes, take it with you.
The whole canvas?
Yes, we have prepared some beautiful colors, so that this garbage will be cleaned up a little.
Yes, I'd like everyone to paint it.
I see. So you want to bring back the garbage with beautiful colors from above.
I see.
That's why you used such a simple color, wasn't it?
Yes, that's right.
I see.
So, we are trying to make people realize our environmental activities through art.
Everyone, please come to the booth.
It was great. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Well, yes, it is in black and white, and black and white has no color, but depending on the person who sees it, he/she can freely imagine the picture, you know, the color.
I am trying to create a picture that will make the viewer have a rich imagination.
I hope that the sea will be beautiful.
Yes, I will take pictures.
No, not really.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, three, two, one, one more time!
Yes, three, two, one. Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Lucky you.
Nice. Nice. Nice.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, it's my first time. I was a little bit nervous. I was so nervous... but there were so many kids...
Oh, Shitomi!
What, what, classmates?
Friends.
Oh, friends... Oh, well, of course, of course...
I saw you.
You saw it?
No, I saw it. I'm glad.
There's a camera in the back, just in case.
Oh, what's up?
I'm a classmate.
He's a classmate.
Classmates.
Oh, my God.
How, how, how, how. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, that's great.
I think it's perfect. Thank you.
I'm glad you made it out.
Come right back.
It's Lodzian. That line's no good.
I see. That story.
No, I didn't get it.
Hood.
Oh, do you want to get some more food?
Yeah. Oh, yeah, just for lunch.
I'm sure there's going to be a lot of stuff here.
See you at the show.
Have a good time.
Good luck. Good luck.
Thank you. Thank you.
Have a good trip.
I'm sorry.
Well, no, I just wrote it.
I feel like a bad guy.
Polluting the sea in the village.
I can't believe I scribbled on such a wonderful painting.
That's not true.
It was a little scary.
But it feels good to write something on a big canvas, doesn't it?
It's true, it doesn't happen very often.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how it turns out.
But what do you want to see happen?
What do you want it to be?
Oh, I'd like to see the blue of the ocean in Murata.
I don't know.
The ocean is close to Murakata, so even though I live there
I used to go to the beach with my friends.
Bathing in the sea...
Yes, I understand.
I'll paint.
Is this okay?
Is it okay if I continue?
You can do it.
Any color you like.
For my brother and sister over there.
What color can I draw?
Hearts!
Thank you very much.
The righteous child.
Hello.
It's fun.
Good morning.
Steper
Car parts.
You in?
What color do you like?
Pink!
I'll make you a pink one, sis!
Are you drunk?
I'm drunk.
How much pink do you like?
I love it!
You can do whatever you want here on campus.
Just give it some color.
That's good.
Go!
Paint a lot!
Oh! You got it?
That's good! That color!
It's like cyan!
You know cyan?
That's amazing!
I love it!
I love it! I love it!
Is it going to be a beautiful ocean?
Oh, there it is!
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming!
Well, it wasn't a good one.
And you know what? You can do it with your finger like this.
Like this, it makes it look like a butterfly.
Wow!
Sounds fun!
How was it for your child?
Isn't it fun? I've never painted something this big before.
That's because I can't do this size at home.
That's great!
You can choose the colors, and it looks fun.
And you're painting it in your favorite color.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Good night, mother.
Push Nuno.
Push the button.
What color do you like?
Three.
Hello.
Hello, everybody.
Would you like to see it?
I want to see it.
Katza!
Oh, no, one more time.
Oh, one more time.
Oh, here it comes!
What kind of garbage is this? It's packed.
Boober. It was fun making a dragger.
It was fun. What did you imagine I wrote?
I'm going to go with "something
What did you write on the back? Rainbow colors
I wrote "sunset.
I like it. Why did you choose sunset?
I saw a beautiful sunset yesterday.
I wonder if I wrote it...
It's kind of nice, isn't it?
Gonzau.
Specializing in dtc
Boo.
I'd like to see
andel
Can't do camera
Your comments are great!
Your Japanese is very good.
You speak very good Japanese!
Thank you very much.
What do you think? Try it, Miko.
It's embarrassing.
Isn't that enthusiasm?
Like, "I'm going to have fun with this.
It's Japan, after all.
I'm going to eat a lot of Jagariko and go home.
I'm going home with happy memories.
Come in, come in, come in.
Filled to the brim!
Pause!
Thank you very much.
I bow to the Lord, the Lord, the Lord.
Oh, my God.
God is here.
How do we pay our respects?
Can you snap?
You can snap.
What are you asking for?
I don't know.
You don't know? I don't know.
Let's get this day over with.
Tell him to draw one omikuji.
Tell him to draw one.
Mr. fortune, are you going to the hotel?
I wonder.
What was it?
It's a good omen.
What does it say?
It says, "No romance yet.
That's right.
You're right.
Why don't you tie a bow?
Do you have two?
Thank you very much.
What's this one?
Which one?
Shokichi is saying "Inian".
Shokichi.
Let me see. Let me see.
Show it to your brother.
I'm Shokichi.
Shokichi.
What do we have here?
What did I get?
Shokichi?
Shokichi.
Thank you very much.
Where shall I take it?
Take it, take it, take it, take it. Ready?
That hurts.
Here we go.
I don't feel any pain. Not at all.
Okay, okay.
Not at all. You're hurting.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Come here. Come here.
Ha-ha-ha.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work
Fast forward
What are you writing a wish for?
I like Miyu Miyu's erasure.
There's a store at the Gugu shrine.
Can I ask you a question?
Oh, this place is amazing.
My grandpa is 101 years old.
Please let him live longer.
I'd like to hear you on the radio again.
Please do.
I'd love to do radio.
I've been doing it for a while.
There's a lot going on.
Some people are rooting for you.
There's quite a few things.
Her, her.
I want to take a picture with you and Miko.
That'll get it.
Oh, there you are already, Rocky-san.
Mr. Rocky, put your hand on the house.
That's nice.
I heard that you wish for your sister to get into high school.
It's true.
Properly overseas.
Really, Korea.
That's nice.
I wish to be Zaon more than Merle or Nishida
Great, I have to be more than 30 times more
He's very strong.
This is great.
I'm so glad you guys enjoyed it.
It was a little embarrassing.
It was okay, I enjoyed it.
It's fun to meet everyone as it is, so
we'll have a port session after this.
Resito.
You're in a hurry again.
I want to break into each other for the prestigious awards.
Congratulations, Earthling.
What's with you guys?
It's Vegeta!
It's Vegeta.
Mr. Vegeta!
What's the matter?
I won't lose again!
Thank you
You're so cool.
I've never been here before.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You're only 5?
It's Vegeta.
It's Vegeta!
Garrickho, please.
Vegeta!
Vegeta.
Egita's next.
Yeah, you'll be happy to hear that.
It's so cool!
Oh, no, it's here.
Please take the liberty of looking at it and striking a pose.
Oh, that's so cool!
Oh, my God, that's so cool!
Man-man!
I thought you said it wasn't Ikemon!
What's going on here?
It's Vegeta.
There's a mesh that looks like he's doing something.
Look, try it.
Eh, it's cute.
Cute.
Maji Maron.
There's some amazing-looking stuff.
There are so many.
Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, hey, hey, there was a lot of stuff of Mikuni's
Oh!
Thick rose juice.
You like it?
I'd kill you for juice.
Oh!
I don't think he knows.
Excuse me, sir.
What are you doing here?
What the hell?
I could feel your fighting spirit.
That's why I'm here.
Thank you very much.
I'll be on the e-sports side later.
advertisement
And our member Sakura Seta.
That vile bitch.
We'll take him with us.
By all means, join us.
Have fun!
All right.
Thank you.
We're really thirsty right now.
What?
Banana juice.
Maybe some marshmallows.
Marshmallows?
That's cute.
Wanna eat something cute together?
I don't like cute things.
I'll eat it.
Yay.
Hey, girl.
You sure you don't want some thick banana juice?
Yes, sir.
Thick banana juice and...
And a marshmallow section.
Oh, no!
The Final Flush.
There it is.
And marshmallows.
Yeah, and marshmallows.
Let's be marshmallows.
Three banana juices.
Let's drink them together.
Yes, please.
Captel Corporation to the point.
Oh, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Oh, you baked it.
Thank you very much
Bon appétit.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
OK.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
It's pretty rich.
Ta-da!
Rich banana juice.
Let's have it!
Bon appétit.
Hmm?
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Oh, man.
It's so cold.
Delicious.
Venezita.
This is so cold.
The rich sweetness of the banana pops in your mouth afterwards.
Super banana.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yes, it's delicious.
Let's go. Bye.
What?
It's time to go.
Okay.
Good luck with e-sports.
Of course. Bye, Nakadamura.
Bye-bye.
Bleep!
He left like that storm.
What a surprise!
I wonder what time it was.
Good night.
Good luck, Venezita.
No wonder.
Fine bread.
Good night.
Good night. Good night.
Good night, good night
oh yeahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
I'll be back soon with some more mars cactiient
I've got the price to help you...
Man...